Register of the Tom Mboya papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Declassified U.S. government records, 1962
  - 2015 release of records (Box-folder 72: 8)
    Includes meeting minutes and reports of the Kenya Constitutional Conference containing materials from the Committee on the Structure of Government, Committee on the Bill of Rights, and other subcommittees.
- Original correspondence from Barack Obama, 1962 (Reel 48)
  Original copy in box 73 CLOSED. Use copy available in Box/Folder 41: 5